Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/ ngocnguyen0501 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Stakeholder Management Employee Relations HR Management

Languages

English (Professional Working)

Certifications

Organizational Learning and Development

Hire, Retain, and Grow Top Millennial Talent

People Analytics

How to Design and Deliver Training Programs

Creating a Leadership Development Program

Honors-Awards

Best of Ownership Award 2017

Publications

SÁCH: Nghề Nhân Sư Việt - Tập 2

Ngoc Nguyen

HR Manager at Sioux Vietnam & Singapore Da Nang City, Vietnam

Summary

With more than 8 years experience in HR, I have solid experience in Talent Acquisition, People Development, Employer Branding & Employee Engagement with a demonstrated history of working in the IT industry. Skilled in Interviewing, Negotiation and Organizational Development.

Strong human resources professional when completed the program of SHRM (Society for Human Resources Management)

Blog: https://ngocnguyenblog145467659.wordpress.com/

Skype: nhungoc0501

Experience

Sioux Technologies 4 years 1 month

HR Manager

July 2022 - Present (2 years 9 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Scope: Sioux Vietnam and Singapore

Senior Human Resources Officer

March 2021 - June 2022 (1 year 4 months)

Da Nang City, Vietnam

Zalo

Senior Talent Development

March 2019 - March 2021 (2 years 1 month)

Ho Chi Minh City, Vietnam

Zalo is one of the business units of VNG Corporation. Zalo's ecosystem includes Zalo, Zing MP3, Zing TV, Zingnews, Báo Mới, Laban Key, Adtima and several new products.

At Zalo, we believe Vietnamese people have the abilities to bring out worldclass tech products.

Zalo I Zing News I ZingMp3 I Laban I Baomoi I Adtima I ZingTV I KiKi

ZIGExN VeNtura Co., Ltd

2 years 2 months

Senior Human Resources Specialist (Acting leader)

January 2018 - March 2019 (1 year 3 months)

Ho Chi Minh

Human Resources Executive February 2017 - May 2018 (1 year 4 months)

Vietnam

Jetstar Pacific Airlines Research Collaborator February 2016 - January 2017 (1 year)

Hồ Chí Minh

Education

SHRM (Society for Human Resources Management) SHRM CP · (2019 - 2020)

Vietnam Aviation Academy
Bachelor's degree, Business Administration and Management, General

Quốc Học – Huế High School for the Gifted